Amanda Steele Show.
We are in the midst of the group chat topic of the week.
We're talking about advice.
Advice.
Now, let me just tell you, since this damn interview,
the amount of unsolicited advice that I have received,
oh my God, y'all.
It is, luckily, there has been so much positive.
But, you know, people love to just kind of tell you,
you know what you should do?
And you're like, no, I don't.
And I don't want to know what you think I should do.
Because I don't even know what you do.
Right?
Who are you?
Now, who are you?
Now, I will say this.
I believe that you can get good advice from anywhere.
You can get good advice from bad people.
You can get good advice from strangers.
And you can get good advice from, like, even TV.
Like, you can get good advice from, like, even, like, movies.
I mean, one of my favorite quotes is from the movie The Natural.
And she says, there's the life you learn with,
and there's the life you live with what you learned.
Yeah.
I have this one friend who will just hear,
she'll hear random things.
And be like, that was a word for me right there.
It'll be like, it'll be just like something random on the TV.
Like, don't wait to pay your loan.
Pay it today.
And it's like, you know what?
I have some debts that I need to pay.
That's a message for me right there.
So they tapped in with everything that's going on in the universe.
We are, we are, we are.